I think we're going to have a crisis.
There's no question about it.
>> I'm worried about something worse than a
recession. Yes,
>> I believe we are currently on the brink.
Depression is kind of what he's talking
about.
>> You created the mess we're in and now
you're saying sorry.
>> I said to there's going to be more
change in the next 10 years to humanity
than all of humanity's history. You buy
that or not buy that? Forget the 10
years. What's going to happen in the
next 36 months?
We're going to have AGI. There's zero
question. Some say we have it now.
Meaning one AI has more power, more
understanding in mathematics or
chemistry than any human. In 5 to 6
years, we're going to have super
intelligence.
China gets it. They take over the world.
>> Whoever gets quantum will control the
other's military. We don't have to have
the bombs. We can just get the codes and
blow them up where they are. Then
there's robotics. When in 10 years,
there'll be more robots than there
probably are humans. Think about like
electricity. 10 years from now, labor
will be like electricity. In 2008, we
lost 8 million jobs. Almost destroyed
the American economy. What's going to
happen in the next 36 months? There will
be a point where there'll be no truck
drivers, no taxi drivers, no Uber
drivers. You're not going to be replaced
by an AI. You're replaced by somebody
who knows how to use an AI.
Now, we have politicians on both sides
that take advantage of whatever is going
on in the environment for more power. It
has nothing to do with what serves the
American people. The information age
died a long time ago. We're drowning in
information. We're starving for wisdom.
So, I'm going to ask you an indirect way
of helping our guys, our production team
that works so hard get a raise. Do you
want to help them get a raise? This is
how you can help us out. 49% of you
watch our podcast that our editors work
so hard, producers, cutters, all of
them. Our production team, 32 of them
that work here, they work very, very
hard to deliver a good quality to you.
If you enjoy our show and you want to
help this thing get bigger so we can
take our talent that we have in house
that support this production all the
time and maybe even give them a raise
then please subscribe to the channel
that allows us to get more viewership
and indirectly it makes bigger
opportunities for our current team that
we have. Thank you so much. Our goal
today is to get better with investment.
So who we brought in today is the great
Tony Robbins. Every once in a while I
can introduce people with the great and
Tony qualifies. He's the greatest in the
space. So we have the great Tony Robbins
back and we have Christopher not Chris
Christopher Zuk here back with us. I
have to qualify that because it's very
important to make sure we say that who's
back here with us today. And you got a
great story on how you went from having
a half a billion dollars of money under
management. You've been following
personal power for many many decades.
And then all of a sudden Tony invests in
your company. you don't even know about
it even though you've been following
them for nearly 30 years and then you
get even more involved and then now you
guys got nearly $14 billion or so of
money under management which is an
amazing story. So our goal is for our
audience to get smarter today. So I'd
like to start with a game if you can see
what you have in front of you. You have
a buy, sell, and hold sign in front of
you. [laughter] I'm going to go through
different investments. Okay? And we're
gonna start off with value right off the
bat and then we'll get into it. Oh,
gold. Do you buy, sell, or hold gold
today? What do you do?
>> Hold your hold, your body.
>> But, but, but I think that answer all
your questions. They're being asked in
the wrong order.
>> Okay.
>> The dog bit Johnny bit the dog. Same se
same elements, different sequence,
different result. You can't have an
answer to this question if you don't
know what your outcomes are and you have
to know what your asset allocation is.
So right now, for example, if you don't
have anything that's covered in that
category, yeah, which I have very
little, honestly, then it might be an
area that you might want to consider
because it's something that's changing
but based on inflation. But all the
answers you're going to ask for here are
basically based on that individual's
real need. If you start making a
generalization about it, we're going to
giving people the wrong advice.
>> I think that's a good qualification for
you. So this is for you. This is not a
recommendation to others. This is just
[laughter] where you're at. And if on
any one of them you want to unpack. And
remember guys, this is not uh just this
is not financial advice. This is just
they're telling you what their opinions
are. Bitcoin buy, sell, and hold.
>> Sell for you. Okay. You're also sell.
Yeah. Okay. Maybe a couple of these if
you don't mind. I'll come back to
>> Sure.
>> Okay. Uh so how about commercial real
estate?
>> Depends on [clears throat] where.
>> Yeah, I was going to say that's
location.
>> So that's going to be location. So some
areas of cell, some areas. Okay, that's
fine. I like that. So
>> real estate is all local, right? You
have you don't think about it on a
national scale.
>> I think that's I agree. So, uh S&P 500
>> really [laughter]
>> maybe
>> I'm a seller today.
>> I'm going to come back to that one as
well and I we'll talk about that as
well. So, I'm going to put C if you
don't mind. I'm going to put C next to
it
>> and I'm going to put T here. Uh single
family homes. Is it still based on
states?
>> It's definitely still based. So, just
let's just move on. Real estate
neighborhoods. California.
[laughter]
>> You guys are on the same page there.
Okay. Absolutely. Texas.
>> That would be a That would be a buy.
>> That would be a buy. Okay. New York.
>> Yeah.
>> All right. Florida.
>> I'm a holder there.
>> Really?
>> I'm a buyer.
>> You're a buy. Okay. I'm going to come to
you with that one. If you're saying
that, how about Illinois?
>> Illinois. I'm a holder.
>> Really? Okay. That's a blue.
>> I don't know about the market there. I
wouldn't come. You said Chicago would be
a different answer.
>> That would be a sell. Illinois that
would be a hole. There's so many great
parts.
>> Neapville, some of the markets that they
have. Okay, I respect that. Tennessee is
a definite buy.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. So, you guys are both by there.
Collectible cards.
>> Yeah. Again,
>> I'll hold if I own them. I'm going to
enjoy them, but I'm not going to I'm not
going to be a buyer today.
>> Are you in the same place?
>> I wouldn't be a buyer today.
>> Okay, fair enough. Sports teams.
>> No, we we we do that every day. So,
[laughter]
>> we're big buyers.
>> We're then we're definitely talking
about that. nuclear stocks,
>> nuclear power
>> depends on the newest types.
>> You know, the call had with you Tony a
couple months ago when you just broke
down what you're involved in with the
power and nuclear and I don't know what
state it was. Was it South Dakota, West
Virginia where you maybe we'll get into
that later on. It's very interesting the
way you were breaking it down. Okay.
Defense companies
>> definitely buy.
>> Okay. Are you following what Palmer
Lucky is doing with some of the newer
>> drones early with with Palmer on
>> call? Good call. And that thing's going
to go I think that could be a trillion
dollar valuation depending on how much
he scales it. College degrees.
>> Um I'm actually I'm in the place of
showing people how to get those without
spending any money. I've got a new part
portion called Univers United Colleges
of America where we guarantee anybody
with less than $100,000 a college degree
where they get new skills, a new life,
but no debt. The number one debt in
America is mortgages. Number two is is
education. And imagine this 1.8 trillion
people spend four years worth of
education to pay it off over 20 years.
Obama was still paying off as a senator
and he had a bunch of scholarships. His
It is out of control. It is out of
balance. But there are good solutions
and especially if you're getting skills
that are actually in the marketplace.
You know, getting sp borrowing money
that you don't have to get skills that
are outdated for a job that doesn't
exist is not a good formula. And that's
why I think a lot of kids are so upset
coming out of college right now.
>> Would you mind if we come back and
revisit this? Is that something I
definitely want to talk about? Okay.
Nvidia
>> right now.
>> Question.
>> Right now I'm a seller.
>> You're a seller. You're hold.
>> Okay. Fair. Palanteer.
>> I'm a holder right now and an owner for
full disclosure. Okay. Fair Tesla.
>> Tesla hold. And last but not least,
SpaceX.
>> SpaceX. We're holder as well. You're a
holder in that.
>> We hold together.
>> Okay. Fantastic. Again, before we go
into the story, walk me through why
you're on sell on Bitcoin. The last I
think Kramer three weeks ago said he
sold all his Bitcoin. 3 weeks later goes
from 62,000 to 78,000. You saw that
whole story. Maybe you were following
it. Why sell on Bitcoin?
>> So, I only use Bitcoin as a trading
vehicle. So therefore, when it's up
higher, I'm typically a seller. When
it's down low, I'm typically a buyer. So
this is more of a trading
recommendation, not a long-term
investment recommendation. I think
there's a place for it in a portfolio as
a trading instrument. It's got lots of
volatility. You can make a lot of money
or lose a lot of money quickly. But
after this move, I'm a seller.
>> I think you have to look at where are
you putting your money and where are
your returns. I think most people get
into Bitcoin initially out of the idea
that's going to protect you against
inflation. But as you know, the same
people invest in Bitcoin are the same
people investing in tech. So right now
you have 32% of the S&P that's in seven
companies, the Magnificent Seven. The
most we've ever seen as a percentage.
That means 32% of the entire volume of
500 companies are coming from seven,
right? That is an imbalance. The most
we've ever had before is 17%. That is a
challenge waiting to happen. When
technology goes down, all the guys that
have Bitcoin, they have to go sell
because they're leveraged usually, and
you see another price change. So for me,
it's just not the best use of my capital
right now.
>> Respect. And neither one of you are
holding any Bitcoin right now. You're in
there.
>> No. No. I have I have some Bitcoin.
>> You have some?
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. So, you're in the hold side with
whatever you have. Okay. Fair enough.
So, for the audience that doesn't know,
I know the story of how you guys met.
Tony, if you don't mind kind of sharing
how the two of you guys became friends
and then partners.
>> Sure. Well, it started out because, you
know, in 2000, well, after 2008, I've
been working with Paul Tudtor Jones, one
of the top traders in the history of the
world. I've worked with them for more
than 30 years. So, I've learned a lot at
least being around him. And after 2008,
I was so frustrated with the fact that
the people that almost destroyed the
world economy, the punishment they got
was more money. That was the reward. So,
about four years later, I said to
myself, I don't have everything, but I
have access. So, I want to interview 50
of the smartest financial investors in
the history of the world that are alive
today. I've got access, and I want to
see, is the game still winnable? And I
wrote Money Master the Game. and I want
to write write a book that my
billionaire clients would love and
someone just starting the game would
love and we made the number one
bestseller and took off like crazy. I
thought that was it. I'm not going to
write another book. But then I saw
people making dumb mistakes and you know
every market changes and so you have to
know how to deal with the downside. So I
didn't know co was coming but
fortunately I wrote unshakable. I wasn't
going to write another book, but then I
started seeing all these individuals,
young people especially, you're seeing
it today where they see young men
especially, are taking a bunch of money
that think they're going to affirm
investments and they're using it on
sports betting right now. 24% of them
say that's their best long-term
investment. That is a recipe for
disaster. So, what people are trying to
do is make up for time. So, I started
looking around and saying, "Okay, how do
I help people?" Well, you and I both
know that where the smart money goes, if
we look at high netw worth people, where
are their assets? 52% of it's in private
equity and private assets. Only 29% in
the public. And if you look at this
stat, this is one everybody needs to
hear. For the last 39 straight years,
private equity, basic private equity,
not the people we wrote about in this
book, that's the masters in the universe
that we work with. Just basic private
equity, is outstripped, outproduced
every stock market in the world every
year for 39 straight years, right?
That's a pretty amazing track record.
And let's take the S&P 500. Over those
39 years, it's averaged 9%. It's pretty
nice compounding. Okay. But if you had
basic private equity, it's 15.7. That's
74% more per year compounded. So if you
put a million dollars 39 years ago and
forgot about it in the S&P, you'd be a
happy camper. You got just less than 29
million, 28.6 to be exact. If you took
that same money and private equity, it's
worth 293 million, 10fold, or smaller
number. You put 100,000 in, 2.9 million
versus 29 million, right? So the problem
is how do you get access right and the
problem has been up until very recently
some brand new rules that we knew were
coming that's why I wrote the book if
you you had to be an accredited investor
or many times a qualified purchaser you
qualified purchaser you have $5 million
net worth to make some of these
investments the the richest people in
the world get access but even me you
know I've done pretty well and I've a
name like yourself you have a name you
can usually get access but the slice I
get will be so small that it's not going
to change my life and I was lamenting
about this to a friend of mine and he
was a former partner of Paul Tudtor
Jones.
>> Till when did you feel that way that
even a guy like you?
>> Yeah. 10 years ago. Eight years ago.
>> What were you worth 10 years ago?
>> My net worth then probably 400 million
bucks.
>> So even at 400 million, you're not
getting the type of access that the big
guys are getting.
>> I was getting access, but it's like I
want to buy an SP3 Ferrari, right? They
come out, they're $3 million, but
they're all pre-sold to everybody
already.
>> You're paying 5.8 or 5.5.
>> Well, actually a little more now.
[laughter]
>> I see the numbers. So, so one of them
sold for 25 million. I don't know what
>> I think it was 12 or 14. Did
>> you see that? Whatever charity event.
>> I know. I was like, "Oh my god, crazy."
>> But the point is, so getting access so I
would get access, but a small slice. So
I I mentioned this to my friend and my
friend said, "You've changed my life so
much. I'm going to change your life
today." And he's a really sophisticated
investor, right? And he said, "I want to
tell you where I put most of my money."
A guy like this put most your money. I'm
leaning forward. He goes, "There's a
firm." And I'm waiting for him to say
it's going to be in Singapore or London
or, you know, obviously New York,
Connecticut. And he goes, "In Houston,
Texas." And I said, "Houston, Texas,
there's a firm where you don't have to
fight to get in anymore. You don't have
to be a limited partner. You can own a
piece of the firm and own all that they
own." He said, "Tony, you going to own
the horn on the racehorse or own the
racetrack?" He said, "You own the firm.
that means the 2% they charge no matter
how well they do or don't do and the 20%
upside you get I said how is that
possible he said this firm is the best
in it they've been doing it for years
they're leaders in the area you got to
meet him so I flew to meet Christopher
Zuk want to meet this guy and I found
out first of all I got to brag on him
for a second over 25 years he has a 96%
profitability ratio on his investments I
mean how many people on earth have done
that and so I was totally impressed I
saw what he was doing I was like Why
would you ever be a limited partner
again? This is insane. You get to have
all the investments they made in the
past, the present, the future. You get
this massive diversity. When the firm
sells, you get the multiple on the firm
on top of it. That to me was the
greatest thing I could imagine. So, I
got involved with Christopher and then I
started finding all the other
investments that were part of it. And
Christopher um five year about four and
a half years ago, we got together. They
were doing he had been to Well, why
don't you share with him? He had been to
my my seminar years before and started
his business out of it, which I had no
idea. He apparently listened to the
tapes. Was it personal power or which
one was it?
>> So Personal Power back in 1991.
>> One or two?
>> Uh the first
>> the first one.
>> So the you know cassette tapes, you
know, at that time I was working my tail
off but came home late one night and uh
saw Tony doing an infomercial. Loved
what I heard. Ordered the tapes. My wife
and I did the series. One of those days
you do a goal setting workshop. And so
from that workshop I set a goal to start
a firm named Cass Investments within 10
years. And nine years, nine months
later, I started the firm. That
obviously was not a coincidence. I
worked every step of the way to make
that goal a reality. But I'd never went
to a live event until 2013.
In 2013, I went to Day with Destiny,
which totally changed my life. Then I
went to Business Mastery and I
completely redesigned the firm. Already
been around for 12 years at that point,
was successful, but was not anywhere
near what it was capable of being. So,
totally redesigned everything. did not
have anything to do with Tony and and
his family becoming an investor with us
until I literally found out from one of
our team that it had happened, which was
a pretty cool moment because all I do is
talking basically sports analogies and
Tonyms. That's that's basically
everything I do when I'm coaching our
team. So from there, learn more and more
about what he was interested in, what we
were focused on as a business, and how
we potentially could come together. That
obviously led to them becoming a partner
in 2021.
>> So from there, you guys have been
working. So, we've gone from 2.7 billion
to over 13 billion in assets. But what
I'm most excited about is the people,
what we're making available to the
average person.
>> The average person has never had access
to this. You'd have $100,000, $250,000
try to get access, try to get a piece.
We have a hundred firms now, some of the
best on earth. Average firm's $30
billion to give you an idea. And the
types of returns and the type to have
that level of intelligence working for
you. And now we have a fund. Share them
with what what's happened because it's
pretty amazing. One of the things that
we talked about in the book is how we
expected that Congress was going to pass
a rule to where people could take a test
to become an accredited investor and
start being able to invest in things
that only historically very wealthy
people could do or institutions could
do. But in June of 25 actually the SEC
changed the rules. So literally just
over a year ago, they made it to where
there's no accreditation required to
invest in certain funds that own assets
that are very unique and very different
for everybody in the world at a $2500
minimum. No accreditation. So now
somebody can own a piece of a private
equity firm or private asset management
firm, a piece of a professional sports
team, a piece of, you know, Anderil
using that example we talked about
earlier. the things that we are able to
do in the private markets that were
never available, they can do that
literally for $2,500 in a structure
that's now available to literally
everybody in the world.
>> So, a person can become a minority owner
of a team with $2,500.
>> That's exactly right.
>> Like, I wanted to own a sports team
where thing I the Dodgers when I was
growing up, we were totally poor. I work
my ass off to save a little bit of money
so I could go in right field and get a
little get a seat maybe twice in a year.
Now, I own a piece of the team, right?
But when I first started out, I was the
first sports team on was the LAFC. I
have to start that with Peter Goober and
our group. And I had to go through a
year's worth of a microscope to be
approved.
>> Tom Penn.
>> Yes. Tom Penn's one of my partners as
well. Yes. And we had to go through and
it was fun. We designed everything. Came
up the colors, the stadium. It was a
blast doing the thing. Then I moved to
Florida and I wasn't [laughter] there
for most of the games. But I went
through all of that and then the rules
changed to now where certain firms can
actually buy a portion of these
different sports teams. So, you know,
I've got a piece of the Dodgers now. We
got a piece of the Red Sox. We've got a
piece of Golden State Warriors. Um, and
he goes on and on. Different sports
teams, different elements. Now, why is
that important? Let's go back a step.
The holy grail of investing. I wrote
this not only to talk about private
equity because it's more than that. It's
to understand the formula that ensures
you have the least amount of risk with
the most amount of upside. And I didn't
come up with that. I interviewed 50 of
the smartest people in the world. Ray
Dalio is one of the greatest investors
in the history of the world. He and I
became good friends. I went in for a
30-minute interview, left four hours
later, became good friends. And at the
end of my first interview with him, I
asked him, I said, "Look, everything
we've talked about, if there's one
principle that investors need to
understand that's been the most
important principle to your success,
what would it be?" He said, "Tony, I
used to have to think about that a lot.
I thought about it for 15 years, and I
can now tell you, I even call it the
holy grail of investing." He said,
"Here's what it is. If you can find 8 to
12 uncorrelated investments that you
believe in, you reduce your risk by 80%
and you increase your upside.
>> Uncorrelated.
>> Yes. So, for example,
>> gas, oil, technology, finance.
>> Well, no. Well, it depends on where you
are. If they're all in the public
markets, they're going to be correlated,
right? So, think about the easy ones.
Stocks and bonds. They're supposed to
zig and zag, go in opposite directions.
You're protected. One day, one's doing
well. If the other the other one's doing
well. However, that's not quite true
anymore. Most things are correlated in
the public markets. In [clears throat]
2008 and 2020, they both went down and
your your your broker will say, "I don't
know. This is what happens." It happens
always in that nature. That's why you
need private equity, private credit,
private assets, private real estate. You
need to have those other types of tools
and that's where you'll be able to come
up with it. So I looked at that and went
by the way in case I wasn't convinced
that was important which I was. Two
weeks later I was here in Miami and they
did the JP Morgan conference the
alternative assets conference and you
got to be a billionaire to go. I've been
there three times invited me to speak.
Ray Dal is speaking right before me. You
you got to be worth more than at least a
billion. Most people worth 10 or more in
that room. He gets up and speaks. The
last question the guy asked him was
similar to my own. Like what's the most
important thing you've learned? He gives
the exact same piece. Every head in the
room looks down and writes this down.
And it's so simple, but all you have to
do is have that diversification. But
most people think diversification like,
oh, I'll have Apple, I'll have, you
know, nine different stocks. That's not
what we're talking about. We're talking
about diversification where they're
going to move in opposite directions.
You have got a great metaphor you always
use in terms of golf.
>> So, I I mean, I love the way that it's
simple to explain a very complex
concept. And that is that, you know, if
you have a golf shop and all you sell in
your golf shop is sunscreen, well, then
on sunny days you sell a lot of
sunscreen. On rainy days, you don't sell
any. you only sell umbrellas. On rainy
days, you're going to sell a lot. On
sunny days, you're going to sell very
little. But if you have both in your
golf shop, every day you're going to be
a winner. You're going to have something
that is selling. That is something
zigging and something zagging. You can
do the exact same thing with your
investments. But most people never can
get access to that because the public
markets are so correlated. You look at
what's happened because of indexation,
just more and more index funds and
people just putting their money into the
S&P 500, etc. They move together as a
group. So they all go up and down
together. Well, you don't want that as
an investor because you want to get off
the roller coaster. You want to get onto
an escalator where you can have a much
smoother ride.
>> Right. Makes sense. So Christopher, can
you give me the example of 8 to2
uncorrelated investment?
>> So very easy. Sports being right at the
top of the list because we were talking
about it. It has a and I'll give the
technical definition of correlation.
Something is one correlated to the S&P
500 if it moves together with it
basically 100% of the time. Could
different magnitude but basically the
same direction. One to one.
>> Okay. One to one. Zero means no
correlation at all. A negative number
means it moves in the opposite
direction. Okay. Sports has a negative
correlation. Z le less than zero
correlation to the S&P 500. The business
model of sports teams is not what drives
the S&P 500. Every day you have
inflation protection. You have real
estate. You have all these media rights
which are enormously valuable. Here's a
fun statistic for you. Your audience
will really appreciate this. In 2005, 14
of the top 100 watched live programs
were sports. Okay? 14 out of 100. In
2025, 96 of the top 100 are sports
because who wants to watch a commercial
if you don't have to, but you're going
to watch that if it's a live event like
a sporting event, but it doesn't move at
the same time. So, there's one easy
example. Owning a GP stake, owning a
private asset management firm, that's
basically a 0.1 correlation. So 90% of
the time it's not moving in the same
direction. Energy negative correlation.
It moves usually in the opposite
direction. You look at something like
space and defense or venture capital.
There's definitely some correlation but
it's called 30 or 40% correlation as
opposed to public private you know p
public assets in the technology world.
That might be 80 or 90 or 95 in the case
of something like Nvidia because it's
effectively the market. So you want to
have all these assets that are not
zigging and zagging at the same time.
That's what gives you a smoother
smoother ride and gives you the ability
to have a steadier return with less
volatility, less risk by the definition.
But in most cases, you actually have the
ability to make more return. Now,
>> by the way, just take sports for
example, just for a second, okay?
There's been an 18% compounded return
the last 10 years alone in sports teams,
right? And you couldn't even participate
in this a few years ago. Now you can,
but I'll give you an example. my dear
friend and partner Peter Goober, he
bought the Dodgers, $2.2 billion. I
don't know if you remember 2012. And
every article was, "They're insane.
They're going to lose money. It's the
most anybody's ever paid for a
franchise." And I said to Peter's, my
friend and partner. I was like, "Uh,
Peter," I was like, "Uh, are you sure
about this?" He goes, "Do you know me? I
don't know what I'm doing." He goes,
"I'm not going to tell you. I'm going to
make an announcement and then you come
over. We'll we'll have a little
celebration." He announces. Now, bear in
mind, if you and an NBA team, you're one
of 32nd teams. NFL, one of 32nd teams.
You get 132nd of all the revenue that
comes for selling national and
international, but you keep your local
advertising rights. He sold advertising
rights the next week for $7 billion and
added 5 billion in a week. Okay? Now,
these are also monopolies. See what what
you got is you have a legal monopoly.
>> How did the guy previous to him not know
that? Cuz I know he was going through
with a divorce, but how did he not know
that to sell the rights? I know Peter's
in a media business.
>> But but Peter's just a better
negotiator.
>> Is that really all it is?
>> It all comes down to Yes. It all comes
down to who do you know the relationship
>> billion5 billion
>> that is just
>> so but but also he he held out for it
he's a smart negotiator knows what he's
doing right so but to give you an idea
he took Golden State Warriors paid $450
million for them they were the worst
team built the stadium built the team
piece of that team it's pretty amazing
I've got world championship rings from
coaching and working with the team
members one of the most fun experiences
of my life but at the same time it's
worth 11 billion only the Dallas Cowboys
are worth more right so the the amount
of value that can be added because
they're not just selling hot dogs and
their fans are called fanatics. That's
where the word fan comes from. And
they're multigenerational.
>> So it's like you got a monopoly that's
legal. You've got customers that are
built in. And now inflation, they just
raise the price of the hot dog. It
doesn't matter. But now these are media
firms. These are real estate firms. And
so we're involved in that business as
another giant chunk opportunity. Look at
what's happened since the um the the
war, you know, in Ukraine in Iran. We've
completely seen war change. You can't
send multi-million dollar missiles to
take out a swarm of $30,000, you know,
worth of of of swarms that are there
being knocked out. So now you have
Andrew and all these people saying,
"We're going to build the next area of
warfare." Now you can predict what's
going to be spent there because every
government around the world now that's
aligned with the United States, NATO has
asked to spend 5%. So they're going to
go from 3.6 billion to 6.6 six bill
excuse me trillion dollars they're going
to have to spend and there are certain
places that's going to have to go and
the the leaders in this area those are
the ones that we want to own and we own
them early on and those are part of what
our fund is about as well.
>> Yeah I remember a tweet may maybe you'll
remember I'm sure you'll remember this
where Chamat tweeted saying he bought a
10% estate I don't know what it was in
Golden State he put $25 million into it
by the time he he sold he made 25x
return on his money.
>> Yes. And he sold early.
>> He sold early. He could have he could
have made 50x on it. Right. So, here's
another question for you. Within sports,
do you sit there and categorize which
one within the space of sports is better
right now? Like, is it NHL, NBA, MLB,
NFL, MLS? Do you look at it that way as
well?
>> You have to I mean, you have to value
everything based on what the going to
be. Well, the NFL is the 800 lb gorilla.
It is the dominant player by a very
large margin. I mean, it's like three or
four times the revenue production as the
next 16 games.
>> That's exactly right.
If you own a team, your share of the
revenue, not your local revenue,
advertising is around $450 million on
day one.
>> Before you play a game, before you sell
a season ticket, before you do anything,
[laughter]
>> it's $450 million.
>> The CFO of Dolphins is a friend of mine.
So,
>> no, no, and it's it's just a fantastic
business. But what happened was and and
I candidly, I was the skeptic, right? It
took me two years to make a decision to
invest in sports. Two years. Because I
wasn't convinced it wasn't just a trophy
asset. and that everybody wasn't going
to be just doing it to say they owned a
piece of a sports team. What I realized
is that cord cutting was real. The
example I just gave and that is what's
driving the valuation. When the NBA
renegotiated renegotiated their media
rights, it was a 3x step up in the value
of their media rights. Right now, the
NFL, and obviously this is very
wellnown, the NFL media rights that are
currently in place through 2032, they're
at a 37% discount to the NBA rights
today when you look at it on a perviewer
basis. So, in 2029, the NFL has the
ability to renegotiate that. Here's a
fun statistic for your audience as well.
People know Amazon has obviously got
Thursday Night Football, but everybody
thinks about it, okay? They just want to
be able to host those games. The number
one sign up for Prime is every Thursday
night in the fall because if you want to
watch your team and that's the only way
you can do it and you are a fanatic,
you're going to pay for Prime. Now, some
people will cancel, right? But a lot of
people will go, "Hey, this is a pretty
good deal." And they will keep it all
the way through the year. It's a huge
revenue driver for Apple, Amazon,
Google, YouTube, etc. That's why it's
such an immense business opportunity
going forward. Tony, I believe in the
book you guys talk about seven things,
right? If I'm not mistaken, seven
different ways of looking at investment,
sports teams being one of them. What are
the other six?
>> Well, another one you should touch on is
energy. I mean, let's when we first
wrote the book less than two years ago,
this is the paperback coming out, but we
had to update it because there was
nothing in there even about data centers
then. So, you know, I have a place in
West Virginia. I bought a power plant
myself there, 1.3 gawatts, did it with
some partners. It's 8% of electricity
there. Well, that's before data centers
came along. Now the demand for
electricity is so large. It's been
growing anyway based on population and
technology. But with AI, it is the
defense of whether China wins or not. So
we're in a position right now where for
years because of the approach towards
fossil fuels, we were making investments
in those areas. Tell them the types of
deals we're able to make. Right now it's
>> as an example in the private markets,
we're able to look into investments and
make investments at three to four times
cash flow. All right. Now, that's
incredibly inexpensive because contrast.
>> So, the contrast to like as an example,
many of the Magnificent Seven that we
were looking at earlier, they're trading
at 200 times cash flow, right? Or 100
times cash. We're paying three to four.
The reason why is there's not as many
people that are willing to invest in
fossil fuels. And I respect their right
to do that, but I also respect the right
to invest my capital and our capital in
that and make a lot of money because
we're providing what the country needs
and what the world needs. So, when you
>> and we're doing the other sources of
energy as well. Absolutely.
Something we talked about earlier as
well. So nuclear.
>> But why are you long on that? Why why
are you is it because what? Because did
you know that the data centers were
going to go on the boom of you know
right now I think we got like 1500
pending that have to build. It's a very
big political discussion right now. It's
going to be one of the topics they're
going to talk about during midterms as
well as
>> China is the one putting out the
information about it to try to make us
weak and make our population push
against them because if they win that
war they win the war of AI. What do you
say to people in America that are like,
"Tony, I'm I'm against this. This is the
I love you, Tony, but I'm not for AI
data centers being built everywhere, the
sound, the noise. What What's your
position with that?"
>> Well, you need to go and actually find
out the data because the other people
say it's using up all the water and they
don't understand what's actually being
done. They're hearing the story it's
being told. And most of it's by bots
coming in. It's been documented over and
over again by China. If they win on
energy, they will control the world
through AI. That's how important this
is. This is not just oh I like AI I
don't like AI and and I don't tell
people to agree with me about everything
or you can decide to invest in anything
do anything not do anything but you
ought to educate yourself because
otherwise the problem with social media
is most people's news comes from social
media we know most of it is not even
real listen even the top media their job
is not to inform you their job is to
startle you the information age died a
long time ago there's too much
information we're drowning in
information we're starving for wisdom so
they have one job. They're not doing bad
things. They're doing what they're
supposed to. They're supposed to make
money for their investors. The way you
make money for your investors is to get
your attention. That way, that headline,
if it inflames you or excites you and
you click on it, I'm paid. It doesn't
even matter.
>> How does the individual know the
difference between BS and real? How do I
>> That's that that's tough. But there are
some companies out there now that have
filters just like they do what's AI and
what's not. Um that can actually let you
see, okay, this is being published by a
bot. This is being published by someone
far left, far right. A couple of these
filters. I like to do them so I can read
what's real and I like to see a left and
a right point of view when it's
accurate, right? Meaning it's their
perception. They're still based on the
facts, but otherwise you're just being
fed stuff all day long. Where are most
people getting their stuff? They're
getting it not even social. They're
getting from Tik Tok. So they don't have
a clue what's really going on and
they're making decisions that affect
their lives or affect the country. I
mean, let's look at look at communism
right now.
>> When I was 23, I went to the Soviet
Union. I was brought over there because
of doing the firewalk. I was brought
with a group of scientists. They were
interested in interested in paranormal
things. I thought I I wasn't a
capitalist. I didn't know what a
capitalist was. I thought, well, this is
cool and everything's going to be equal
and fair. Like everybody like we're all
going to come by and everything's going
to be free. And guess what I discovered
by spending two and a half weeks there.
I traveled on a train from literally
from one end of the earth to Siberia and
all the way back to Moscow. Two and a
half weeks. Everyone I traveled with,
they had on the train. They were all
comrades. They're all equal. We had
caviar. We had champagne. We had
everything you could possibly imagine.
Every single town we pulled into is the
same ugly gray area. Giant building and
people wrapped around in the freezing
cold every single day when we landed the
next city. Stop stopped the next city.
And what it was is people standing in
line to get a quart of milk and half a
loaf of bread. When you see what
communism and socialism brings, you
understand like down in Cuba, listen,
Castro said he wasn't a communist. He
said he wasn't a socialist. He said he
was for free elections. He said it was
free everything. We have a society of
people that we have failed to show them
how important free enterprise is in our
country. The reason kids are suffering
is we have not taught them any history
and they're all consumers. Listen, if if
you have a Apple phone, which most
people have an iPhone, a large number of
people do, say, how many did you buy? I
I showed some kids the other day. Here's
what it would if you bought every
iPhone. It came to I think it was like
$22,000. If you would have taken the
same amount of money you spent on the
iPhone and you became an owner instead
of a consumer, you bought the stock of
Apple for the same price as that phone
at that time, I showed him exactly what
it is, you'd have $331,000
right now. It's not an economic problem.
It's that you're a consumer, not an
owner. And we need to teach people to be
owners. And so we show people how to do
that though in a way that has that a
huge advantage. Like yes, we got massive
inflation right now that's been
stimulated by multiple generations, but
certainly during co we spent three and a
half to four trillion dollars more than
we needed to spend during that time and
everybody thought it wouldn't have
created inflation and it has so we have
to deal with that inflation right now.
we have something being fought, a war
being fought to try and keep, you know,
nuclear weapons from being, you know, in
the Middle East, you know, being used.
All that is plays a certain role. But I
did an analysis with a group of people
and looked at all the things that we buy
today. And the generation that thinks
they can't afford anything. There's only
three things that are more expensive
than any other generation. Everything
else is cheaper. You're old enough to
remember that if you wanted, I'll give
you some funny example. Music. Did you
ever go to a music store and buy music
in your age? CDs
>> warehouse.
>> Yes, that's right. We all went
someplace. And you How much did it cost
you to get 12 songs?
>> I don't know. But I know one I would buy
singles for 99 cents. So $14.99 whatever
it was.
>> Yeah. Well, you very few people got
singles in those days, right? You got
them on CD.
>> I didn't have that kind of money. I was
buying single. Easy e hip hop is what I
was.
>> Fantastic. Most people were buying an
album cuz that's what they bought in
those days and it was like 14 15 bucks
for it. Right now $8 and you have a
hundred million songs in there in your
pocket. Crazy. Right? If I want to go on
a date with a girl, I had to be able to
pay eight bucks each and pay for the
dinner. I couldn't Netflix and chill and
have every movie 8,000 movies available
the moment I wanted to. So, I'm being
humorous, but it's true. The three
things that are more expensive. Housing,
that's a local problem. That's a
political problem, right? Because there
are people not being allowed to build.
Like LA, here's a perfect example of how
bad that can be. New York, very, very
similar example. But the other two is
education, which is out of control and
its costs. And that's why kids are so
upset. They've paid all this money.
They've gone in massive debt. And but
that can be changed. And this the last
one for us is healthcare. Those three
are higher. Two of those three I'm
personally working on to help people
with solutions on. I can't do the
housing one by myself. That one people
people have to do. But everything else
is cheaper. And by the way, even in
housing, the average size home for this
generation is twice the size of the last
generation. Average square footage.
People don't compare apples to apples.
But here's what we do today. We look at
social media and you compare to a
billionaire. Okay. Well, there's 3,200
billionaires in the world of 8 and a
half billion people. We used to compare
to our neighbor. So now people are
dissatisfied. They also compared to
somebody who's a phony who's making
themselves look better than they are,
act better than they are, behave better
than they are, and then people feel
inferior and get angry. So our solution
is look, you need to take advantage of
the system that's here. The game is
still winnable, but you got to educate
yourself. You got to get the skills.
You're not going to be replaced by an
AI. You're going to be replaced by
someone who knows how to use an AI. So,
let's get you the skills. Let's get you
an investment skills so you can secure
your financial future. Let's get you the
personal skills so you can do well in
your personal life. Let's get you the
business skills so you can do well there
as well in your career.
>> I want to get into that. And so, but but
on this by the way, real quick, before
23, were you into like what's communism,
capitalism, were you into were you into
none of that stuff? So, it inspired you
afterwards when you left? But because I
thought it was going to be all equal
like what these kids are being sold just
like what Castro sold. Go down to Cuba
see what it's like. I've been there.
Yeah. You don't want to go anybody here
in South Florida will tell you there's
no way they're going to allow us to have
socialism here. So but but it's a
delusion that things are free.
>> So So this gets me to think about
something Tony. Your mind is very
creative. So I'm curious what you would
say or Chris what you would say. So you
know when you when you look at Mormons
the church I'm not you're going to see
what direction I'm going. I'm going to
come back to a good place. I work with a
lot of Mormons for a long time. I know
you have as well. You know, you go to a
lot of these sales organization. Utah,
it's filled with a lot of Mormons. They
get their kids when they turn 18, 19,
they go on two years. They go on a
mission and then they come back and
they're able to learn a language within
six weeks. So, the FBI is trying to
learn how Mormon uses. So, how do you
teach these people this language so
quick? They go like Nick Shirley who's
doing great great work. He's Mormon. So,
he doesn't have a problem going to these
countries. You see sometimes Israel when
somebody wants to go back and see the
country they will bring people back to
show them how special it is and you see
how much Jews have a lot of pride in
what they have. What can we do as
Americans to take our youth to send them
somewhere fund it to realize how great
America is so we minimize the amount of
socialism that's starting to spread
amongst the youth. What can we, if you
were the Secretary of Treasury, Tony
Robbins, what would you do to get some
of these young kids to realize how
amazing America is?
>> Well, I think
>> handcrafted across five Italian
factories with builder technology
underfoot, it may be [music] the most
comfortable shoe you will ever own.
Introducing the allnew FLB shoe.
Finished in new chocolate cura leather.
Made to move, built to [music] endure,
designed to impress.
>> You know, most people we a belief is a
poor substitute for an experience. You
can believe what America's like when you
haven't compared. You saw all the people
coming here, you know, during the the
the World Cup time and they're raving
about America and their view of America
has been done by the media. The same
media that's convinced Americans that
this is a terrible place. So, it's nice
to see how the rest of the world
actually sees this when they're actually
here. They were excited about the size
of our burgers and whether you could
have ranch dressing, but everything that
people take for granted in this country,
they take for granted. Not because
they're not good people, they just don't
have an experience. So, anything gives
them the experience would do it. If I
was president of the United States
though, the thing I would do if I had
the right, and you can't, is I would
definitely have a national service.
Like, you know, in Israel, as you know,
once you turn 18, everybody joins the
service. And by the way, if you're, you
know, 120 or 130 above in IQ, they put
you in MSAD, they put you in AI. And
that's why there's I have partners there
because there's a concentration of
intelligence there that like no other
place on earth for the for the size of
the population. But when you serve, it
helps you see other worlds. That's what
these Mormons do, too. They get to see
how good it is here. they get to serve
also and feel their life is about
something more than themselves. When we
think it's only about us, we get angry
because we're not made to just get.
We're made to give. Anybody who has
really experienced something where they
care about something more than
themselves, whether it's your children
or whether it's something in your
community or it's your company or it's
your county or whatever it is, there's
an energy that human beings have. That's
what's makes us human. When there's
something we're here to serve, life is
calling to us. It's like, you know, we
don't really have a vision in this
country anymore that's strong enough for
people to be called. John F. Kennedy
used to have the famous phrase, don't
ask what your turn can do for you. What
can you do for your country? Our whole
thing is, what are you doing for me? And
you're not giving me enough now and I'm
a victim. So, I think we have to give
that example by showing people that have
succeeded from nothing. It's same thing
with rich people. I had someone the
other day saying, well, we should take
all the money that uh Elon has can pay
for all these things. Elon doesn't have
all this money. He's call him a
trillionaire. It's all in businesses.
It's all buildings that's creating
things. Has Have you ever seen
communists? Did they create a cell
phone? Did they create AI? No. That's
not done by governments. That's done by
individuals who take risks with their
capital. And so we if we could divide
all that up, I I did a video years ago
where I showed if you took all the
richest people in the United States, you
took all the sports teams, you took and
you you killed them all and took all
their money, you can't cover the US
government for a year, right? And you
lose who's going to produce the value
going forward. So our mindset has to
shift if we're going to succeed. And
I'll tell you when it starts to shift,
when you start to become an owner
instead of just an operator or consumer.
If you're a consumer, you're always
stressed. And you don't have to have a
lot of money. Even a tiny amount of
money where you start to put that aside
as a discipline and you start to see it
grow, then all of a sudden you say,
"This is different." This is why the
Trump accounts are so valuable. You
know, Michael Milin and these guys
helped push this out. You can take your
kid if they're born from 25 to 28 during
this administration, $1,000 is given to
them. You can now even your employer can
donate $2,500 a year to them. We were
just uh with the Secretary of Labor
yesterday, um Sandling, and he was
talking about how this is creating a new
generation. We're at 18. these kids can
have $300,000. Now, the next piece is
not to spend $400,000, in my opinion, on
an education where skills don't matter
and now you're in debt. That'll make
anybody angry. So, I understand why
these kids are angry. I'd be angry, too.
They've been sold a bill of goods. But
still better than anywhere else. And you
still got to do something with it. We've
all had things that are unfair and
unjust to us. Anybody who hasn't had
that is going to have it sometime in the
future.
>> You think the government can play a role
on affordability? I know you said some
of the things is local. I'm doing
something with health and I'm doing
something with education.
>> Well, let me give you let me give you
education is a simple example. Okay.
Right. So, let's look at what's
happening right now.
>> If I said to you, there's going to be
more change in the next 10 years to
humanity than all of humanity's history.
Do you buy that or not buy that? I'm
>> I do.
>> Yeah. Me, too. But, you know, when it's
10 years out, that's a way out. So, when
I said I'm going to feed provide a
billion meals 10 years from now, makes
you feel good. But you're not called to
do anything today. But when I go, okay,
that means this year I got to provide a
100 million meals and it took me 37
years. I had no money myself to get fed
to feed others. Finally, I fed 42
million people in 37 years. Now I got to
do 100 million in one year. I got to
find a new way to do this. So with
technology, I take people and say,
forget the 10 years. What's going to
happen next 36 months? I'll give you
three things. Three technologies. A,
we're going to have AGI. There's zero
question. Some say we have it now.
Meaning one AI has more power and more
understanding in mathematics or
chemistry than any human. In five to six
years, we're going to have super
intelligence where one AI will have the
power of all human brains combined. Now
I'm talk I was talking to the vice
chairman of IBM Gary Con who's 10 years
he ran Goldman Sachs had dinner with him
and I said are we winning? I'm I'm
concerned you like there's no safety on
AI. There's you know everybody going for
a trillion dollars. That's the target.
That's the carrot and the stick is if we
don't do it, China gets it. They take
over the world.
>> And he goes, Tony, we're slightly ahead.
But here's what matters more.
>> He said, if you're concerned about that,
you should understand what's happening,
you know, with quantum. Cuz he said,
whoever gets quantum will control the
other's military. We don't have to have
the bombs. We can just get the codes and
blow them up where they are. And he
said, if your friends are worried about
their cryptocurrency, be worried about
the banks. He said, because we have some
anti-quantum right now. it's us in in he
said Google we're the leaders right now
and he said but uh you know JP Morgan
has it but Bank of America doesn't city
bank doesn't he said so the president's
going to do an executive order saying if
you're doing business with the
government you have to have this but he
said it could happen very quick I said
when when's it going to happen he said
less than 36 months I was like and then
the next day I called my friends in
Israel there's six people there that
have quantum companies talk to them all
everything they're doing is less than 36
months and there could be a spark at any
time then there's robotics if you met
Brett yet bigger AI
>> if you go to if you go to California
sometime they'll set you up go there you
walk in his place and it's not like
those robots you see then from China
where they're doing automated automated
stuff karate all that stuff right these
are thinking operating they're
everywhere it's like you're in another
universe they're doing everything you
can imagine they're running everything
making things happen that's happening as
we speak and that within 10 years will
be more robots than there probably are
humans think about like electricity you
don't think about electricity when you
go someplace you don't think about
what's going to cost you know the power
will be there 10 years from now labor
will be like electricity so we have to
think differently so if that's true
what's that going to disrupt number one
business if you don't have agents in
your business they're not getting
implemented right now because people are
afraid so I have a company that does
implementation where instead of
replacing you we do do an analysis for
you of everything you do and have you
see 40 to 60% of what you're doing is
boring work to you it's it's you know
you're supposed to be head of strategic
marketing and you're making a PD PDF,
right? So that we give you an assistant
that does all that for you, a digital
robotic assistant. You get to just work
on strategic elements. Now you're 10
times more value the company. We don't
need to replace you. So there's that
part. And so I'm working with the UAE.
I'm also because they want to make their
government agentic and we're working
with Mark Benoff here at Salesforce. I'm
going to be doing a big presentation to
all the companies there. They're coming
up at Dreamforce. Then the next part,
res-killing America. I remember being
with Obama 10 years ago and saying, "Mr.
president. I said, "You inherited 2008.
It wasn't your fault and you've done as
good a job as any to try to manage
through it." But I said, "You can
prevent the next 2008 if you have some
vision." And he said, "What are you
talking about?" I said, "Well, in 2008,
we lost 8 million jobs, right? Almost
destroyed the American economy." I said,
"There's some technology right in front
of us." And we didn't know AI like we do
now. Then I said, just look at
self-driving cars as one example. I give
you agriculture. I give you 10 examples.
istic self-driving cars. Sometime in the
8 8 to 12 years,
there aren't going to be any truck
drivers. Who's going to pay a truck
driver to drive 8 hours a day when I
have a truck and do it 24 hours a day,
not make mistakes? The insurance is
cheaper and no health insurance and I
depreciate the asset. There will be a
point where there'll be no truck
drivers, no taxi drivers, no Uber
drivers, and there's 8 million. That was
then, there's more now. 8 million in the
economy. That's one category. And he
said to me at the time, he said, 'Well,
Tony, we think that's going to take 20
25 years. And I said, 'Well, Mr.
President, with all due respect, what if
you're wrong? And he said, 'Well,
there'll be new jobs. I said, ' There
will be new jobs. 150 years ago, 90 85%
of us were farmers. Now it's 3% of
America. We feed the whole world with
technology, but we had 150 years come up
new jobs. I said, there's an early
disruption that we have to deal with.
And he goes, well, we got basically too
many fish to fry. And I respect that. He
was going through hell at that time, but
today everybody knows it. So, I look at
this and say, "How are we going to
retool the country?" I I got a
60-year-old brother-in-law who just got
laid off two months ago, software
engineer. They all told you to become a
software engineer.
>> And now, of course, Vibe comes along.
Now, you don't even Vibe. Now, all of a
sudden, your AI does it. Your Gentig AI
does it in a heartbeat. Gary Con's
daughter, he told me, used to get a
million dollars to crush code, right? I
don't 100,000 pieces down to whatever
the number so it's more efficient. Now,
she doesn't have that job anymore as of
this year cuz an agent can do it in a
few days. Now, she's pregnant. They have
a lot of money. She has a new mission.
He's not worried about her. But my
60-year-old brother-in-law walks in, no
severance. 650 people are let go of on
the spot. They sold the company to a
Swedish company, made it a Gentic. And
guess what? He's got two kids in
college. He's got a wife that works
substitute teacher at $30,000 a year,
and he's got a mortgage to pay. So,
here's what I have. United Colleges of
America. You can go to unitedcolges.org.
We offer everybody debt-free education
and it's based on jobs that are actually
available today. So we look at it this
way. Head, hands, and heart. Head is
you're a technology person. You go.
Guess what? Software not working so
well. Well, we can turn you into
software engineer at a different level
on AI where now you make $200 to
$500,000 and the jobs are dying and
waiting for you. And by the way, you're
taught by an AI that knows everything
about you at a pace you could not learn
normally and it's tied to a normal true
college university where you get your
degree as well. So you get it all and if
you make less than $100,000, we pay for
it all. You would put no money out of
your pocket. Now if you lost your job
making 180, you make less than $100,000.
You're already in it immediately. To
give you an idea, we do the same thing
with hands. These truck drivers, tell
them they're not going to have a truck
driving job. They now need to reskill.
Now, we need 500,000 electricians right
now. You started $85,000. You make
$250,000 as top electrician. It's not
going away. Hart, we need 500,000 nurses
right now. 95,000 were turned away last
year. We need them desperately. They
make $100,000 a year.
>> It's the whole head, hands, heart.
>> Yeah. And so, I'm now making all that
agentic though because here's what
education has learned.
>> So, can I ask you this question on your
So, what's your brother-in-law going to
do? Who's your brother-in-law?
>> We just gave him a he just got a
scholarship. He's studying now to do AI
engineering like Phoenix University.
>> How soon is he going to replace his job?
How soon will
>> he'll have it in 18 months?
>> So for the next 18 months, what's he
going to be doing?
>> He's got a certain amount of money that
he's doing. He's still applying for
other jobs and so forth. He's finding
the balance, but so he needs a long-term
solution with let's stay on this because
what you just described is what a lot of
people are concerned about and it's very
personal to you, brother-in-law. So for
a guy that's watching this right now
saying, "Tony, that's my concern. If
these software engineers are being
replaced and these guys were making 250
a year, 150 a year, 300. Some of them
are making $800,000 you depending on how
good they are. What do I do now? My
worry is I'm going to lose my job now.
How do I replace it in 18 months?
>> I I what I would be doing right now is
going then go to United Colleges and we
have an AI that walks you through what
are the opportunities, what are your
skill sets, what's the direction, what
you trying to accomplish. It's better
than most counselors. We had live
counselors. They would complain. People
tell me tell me some information. They
talk forever. Our AI has endless
appreciation and respect for you and
guide you through it to help you figure
out where it is and then you apply for
the scholarship and then when you apply
for it, we then govern where we go.
Right now we have over 100,000 people
that have already signed up and are
getting scholarships as we speak and
we've done that in four months. We're
going to have a million people in the
next 36 months. Our biggest piece now is
locking down the right universities. So
we're right now in negotiations with
several universities who now maybe they
have 3,500 people in a 13,000 person
university that are online and it's an
online online is is not a great
experience for the most part but an
agentic AI that individually meets your
needs this is what they it's called the
two sigma component if you we start out
with education for mass audience I'm
pretty good at that I can do that pretty
well not everybody can smaller class
size got you one sigma better result the
only thing that blows everything away is
you could take an average student if you
give them one-on-one mentoring they
outproduce 98% of the CA class but it's
been too expensive
>> but now with AET AI it's not so we have
the systems in place we're doing it as
we speak so that's one solution I'm not
saying I have the whole solution but
it's a solution for people to start to
reskill so they don't wait till there's
a problem or if they are in a problem
they can take action now
>> at 17 years old you you had a dream of
being a president one day right and and
you've now advised billionaires
athletes, you know, celebrities, actors,
presidents, prime ministers, you name
them. You've sat with everybody. Uh
2028, I'm calling the free agency year
of presidency.
>> And at 28 2028, I think you're going to
be 68 years old. I'm doing the math for
you cuz you're you're a young 68-y old.
>> Yes.
>> If if I'm a betting man, should I
consider putting some money on Khi or
you know, Khi of Tony Robbins running in
28? Because I know RF wanted you as a
VP. He spoke to you about it, right?
That was
>> Yeah, that was his first choice. We
spent a month going back and forth about
whether be his vice president or
candidate.
>> Are you entertaining it?
>> No, I'm not. The I made that I I spent a
month looking at it, made the decision.
The main reason um is that if men and I
do that, half the country can't talk to
unfortunately where we are right now. I
want to serve people. I've I'm an
independent. I I' I've served
Republicans and Democrats. I've served
people on both side of them done work
with, you know, Clinton all the way back
to Reagan I got to do some work with.
Right. So, it's like I want to be able
to help everyone I possibly can. So, I'm
not here to divide that. And I think I
can do more from the outside than the
inside.
>> You still believe that? You still
>> I really do. When I was younger, I
thought that would be the position.
>> So, let me ask you, is there any chance
anybody can change your mind? [laughter]
>> Maybe my wife, but I doubt seriously
she'd rather have it not happen.
>> She probably would rather not you not do
it better.
>> I also, you know, co was good to me. I
have five kids and five grandkids. I
have a 52-y old daughter and I have a
5-year-old daughter thanks to CO. Co was
good to me. So, so [laughter] I don't
know that I want to disrupt that stage.
Uh I'm just turned I'm 66. So I want the
next uh you know 20 years or so to be
being able to contribute as many ways I
possibly can to humanity. Make the
biggest difference. I mean I said I was
going to feed a billion people. We did
that in 8 years. I then said we're going
to do a 100red billion people. I think
you know and I came up with this 100
billion challenge to do in 10 years. I
can't announce it here because I'm
announcing it at the UN in September.
But I can tell you we've outstripped the
hundred billion by a long number. Right?
These were numbers that seemed
impossible. I I I have food for myself.
So, I'm into the scaling of solutions.
That's what I love. And when we kind of
come back to this, the number one
challenge for people though, most people
besides their emotion and psychology
>> is just that they don't know how to take
advantage of the system that's here. And
you don't have to make it so complex.
You can do this. Can we do this? This is
a professional communicator. I mean,
he'll do laps around any one of us. Can
you do me a favor?
>> Go on Twitter. Handle I think what's
what's Tony's handle on Twitter? What
What is your handle on Twitter? Can we
say Is it Tony Robbins or Anthony
Robbins? It's Tony Robins. Is it Can you
look it up? Tony Robbins. Okay. Tony
Robbins.
>> Go on Twitter, Tony Robbins. Tweet and
make an argument why he ought he ought
to consider 2028 [laughter]
running. And by the way, I'd love to see
some of the ideas. FYI, for some of you
that actually want to communicate with
him directly, you can connect them as
well. So, we're going to put the MC QR
code below. But, uh, if you would like
to see that, let's see some of the
arguments and tag me as well. Put PBD
podcast. I'll go look at all the tweets
and maybe we'll get some of his
attention collectively. Maybe we can
make
>> you don't have to be in office to come
up with solutions. In some ways, you
have more freedom outside of office.
>> I think but I think there's I think
there's certain times in life that
responsibility comes on where some
people are gifted with certain things
that's not duplicatable that we we ought
to consider it. And I'm just encouraging
as a friend take that as a compliment.
Let's talk investments. Question.
>> So, you know, you said something you
said $2,500 earlier, right? Nowadays
when they change it it can go all the
way down to 20 25,000. I remember when
it used to 2500 I'm sorry 2500 25,000
was a number where 10 15 years ago we
were talking like my god I talked to uh
who was the former controller general of
the US David Walker I think was his name
and he was working with this uh one man
who uh uh was uh running a portfolio
that you can put $30,000 and that was a
big deal. So 2500 walk me through
levels. Okay [snorts]
I only have $10,000. Mhm.
>> I'm making $80,000 a year. I only have
$10,000. Go to h 100,000. Go to a
million. Go to 10 million. Does it
change at all on what you would consider
me doing? And the age I will choose
>> for the $10,000. Put me at 30.
>> For the $100,000, put me at 40.
>> For the million dollar, put me at 50.
For $10 million, put me at 60. What do
you do with your investment?
>> The answer is it absolutely should
change over time as somebody gets closer
to retirement. It should be based on the
amount of time they have to be invested
in something. You don't invest in a
professional sports team or and or
something like that for a couple of
weeks. You just don't do that. That's
trading. You can trade Bitcoin if you
want to, but you don't invest long term
for that. So, what I tell everybody all
the time is don't think dollars, right?
Don't think dollars at all because it's
all not relevant. Only thing that
matters is percentages. So for the
$10,000 portfolio investing 5% you are
going to invest 500 bucks. Obviously at
100 million you're going to be doing $5
million. The key is to not get tripped
up by the dollar amount being what's
driving somebody because what happens to
that same person like I remember when I
only had 10 grand. So 10 grand is a
whole lot of money to me. Well if you
got a hundred million 10 grand is not
going to move your portfolio one iota.
So you need to make sure that you think
in percentages. And that also removes
the emotion from the equation. What
happens to so many investors is they get
stuck with the emotion like, "Oh, I
bought Nvidia. It went up a little bit.
I got to sell it." Or, "It went down a
little bit. I got to I got to get out."
Whatever it may be, that's a bad
decision to make. They need to
understand why they own something, size
it correctly, and that allows them to
stay with it over time. So, that $10,000
investor, you absolutely have room in
your portfolio for a lot of things. I
wouldn't probably suggest $2,500 of the
10 to go into something that's not
totally liquid simply because you might
need it. Once you get to $100,000,
absolutely, you should have alternate
investments in your portfolio. Again,
assuming the age that you gave of 40.
And then as you get more and more
wealth, you should have a larger and
larger percentage because you don't need
as much liquidity. I'll tell you a
story. I had a gentleman that literally
started with me in 1992 as an investor.
He's now worth well over $500 million.
When I started working with him, he was
worth like 500 grand. Okay.
>> What a great testimony.
>> Obviously, I didn't make all that.
>> I understand it. But was he holding
paper or how did he make his 500 500
million business and obviously
compounding wealth over time? And we
have done a very good job on
>> Can I stop you? Right. Can you So, can
you do me a favor? Because he said
something. He said 10 years ago he was
worth 400 million. And he had access,
but not as much as he's got access
today. Sometimes when you're a good
earner, you're not a good investor. No.
>> And and I had to shift that mindset and
realize, look, I know how to make money.
I know how to make money. Now this can
really grow. Of the half a billion net
worth that he has today, how much of it
came from his exit? How much of it came
from the investment, you know,
compounding?
>> Probably about 400 of it came from his
business either through earnings or his
exit that he had and over a 100 million
of it came from earnings on his
investments over time because obviously
a lot of it happened later with his
exit. But the point is is that he always
always invested the same dollar amount
every single time whether he was worth
$5 million, $10 million, $25 million
wise. Yeah.
>> Just as dollars dollars, not the same
percentage.
>> Interesting.
>> He just he was like in his mind as it
got older, as as he got more wealth, he
was like, I put a million dollars in
everything. I'm like, dude, you're worth
a hund00 million. Putting a million
dollars now is not a lot of money. Gets
to $250 million. I'm putting a million
dollars in. Well, that's crazy. It's not
even relevant. And the the psychology,
going back to what Tony said, is that he
remembers how hard it was to make his
first million. And so, he was literally
stuck with, "I can't do more than a
million because if I lose it, I'm just
going to just beat myself up all day
long because I know how much a million
dollars."
>> He needs this guy if he's got a limiting
belief.
>> Well, he had me fortunately because I
learned a lot from this guy. Makes
sense, right? And so, I was able to tell
him, look, you know, do this. Just put
20 basis points of your net worth into
this investment. Now put 40 basis
points.
>> That's a better strategy. Absolutely the
percentage. So if that 30 basis points
does have a bad outcome, you know, it's
gonna stink, but it's not gonna fatal.
>> So that is the psychology that somebody
has to have. So somebody can do that
when they look at the overall percentage
of their portfolio. Maybe it's 10% to
begin with.
>> We talked about with Secretary
Sonnerling yesterday about 401ks.
There's 14 trillion dollars in 401ks.
They cannot invest in alternative
investments today.
>> So that's about to change. That's
totally changing. Yeah.
>> So now you're talking about for these
people that are making investments in
their 401k, do the right percentage,
allow it to grow, get all the tax
benefits, etc. But you have to have the
psychology of what's the right
percentage. And you know, I know Tony
gave earlier, but I just want to remind
the audience when you look at the
results of the family offices, large
family offices, endowments, foundations,
they have anywhere between 35% and 60%
of their net worth in alternative assets
in private assets. They don't need as
much liquidity, so they have a larger
percentage, giving them the opportunity
to make a higher rate of return. That's
what I would advise anybody along their
path to remember. By the way, just go
ahead.
>> Go ahead. I just want to mention the
most people's biggest reason for losing
money has nothing to do with the
capacity of the investment. It's their
emotions. So they you know the average
year in the last 100 years the market
has had a 14% correction at some point
14%. Now some areas it's bigger but most
of those never turned to a 20 or 30.
They didn't turn into bare markets right
the vast majority did not but people get
panicked since they can push a button
since they have liquidity they do and
that's how they get in pain. Most people
make money on their own private real
estate, their own home that they own.
Why? Because they can't push a button
and get rid of it. So, a portion of your
investments, you should be thinking in
terms of long-term. And as a result of
that, you're going to have a higher rate
of return if that money is tied up
potentially with a place where they're
producing greater results, but you don't
have as much liquidity. So, that's the
balance that has to be found for
anybody.
>> That does make sense. By the way, he's
talking about robots. 10 years more
robots. Elon talked about it. There's
going to be more robots. I think we're
going to sell 10 to 30 million robots.
and he was like, "Wait, what? Yeah, I
think Tesla's going to sell 10 to 30."
And the way he answered it was like,
"That's not a big deal, right?" He
talked about this last year. We all saw
that clip. How do you feel about what's
happening with companies like Autopilot
that they're able to go get the 13F
filing of what Jim Simons was doing with
Renaissance Technology who has been
doing 49% and I can match their 13F
filings and I just put it in there. You
know, the whole Nancy Pelosi trader, the
upside down Kramer. What do you think
that's going to do to the market? Do you
believe in that concept? What what do
you think that's
>> most of that is more marketing than
substance because even on the 13F
filings there's a huge delay there is
>> but between now and the time you don't
know when they sell you know they've
sold it so it's totally gone you know
the Nancy Pelosi or the Jim Kramer
Kramer things you know those are great
marketing they may work they may not it
really doesn't drive things near as much
as the just reality of indexing because
the amount of indexing that has happened
in our country and around the world that
is what's created this concentration
that's what's created all this
correlation to where when things move
they move in the same direction. A very
simple portfolio that was well
diversified in 2005 had an average
correlation crossorrelation as it's
called of 0.16. Remember one is fully
correlated zero is not.16. Today that
exact same portfolio in the exact same
weights is 65. Nothing's changed with
those assets other than the
concentration and indexing that has
happened that when people are sellers
everybody's a seller. When people are a
buyer, everybody's a buyer because when
you buy the ETF, you buy that index
fund, they have to literally be a seller
or they have to be a buyer. There is no
in between.
>> So in stress environments, when the
market gets stressed, correlation goes
up. That exact same portfolio. In stress
environments, average correlation is
over 85%.
Everything gets hammered at the same
time except for a few assets. That's why
the holy grail of investing is so
important. That's why it has to be
things that truly are less correlated or
not correlated at all in somebody's
portfolio to get them off the roller
coaster, get them on the escalator.
>> You're a big fan of Ray Dalio. Ray
Dalio. Uh I spent some time with him at
his Bridgewwater. He's right across in
Aron, right? Right by IBM, I think where
his headquarters is at.
>> He has been talking about many signs. We
just crossed $40 trillion of debt,
right? And he's been talking a lot
about, hey, all the signs of the Great
Depression, all the signs. And I think
he's got a video on YouTube that he did
that's like 45 minutes. If you can go
YouTube, type in Ray Dalio, solve for
filter, go to views on his channel.
Maybe just go to his channel. This
video's got
50 million views and it's not like it's
a short video. Go to his channel right
there. Principles by Ray Dalio. If you
can go to videos and then go to popular,
please. Where is that at? Holy
What does it say? 409 million views.
Second one. 202 million views, right?
These are not small numbers. These are
ridiculous numbers to get. He believes a
possible depression type moment is
around the corner. Do you agree with
them?
>> Well, I agree with him that that's not
exactly what he believes. What he
believes is there is a pattern that has
happened throughout human history and he
studied more than 500 years of history
to see what has that pattern been. And
the pattern is how countries grow. Just
like a kid grows, we have different
stages. Look, if you're a toddler,
you're going to get in more trouble than
if you're just an infant, right? Because
you can do different things. Teenager
goes like crazy. You mature. You get a
little older. You get a little older,
you make different types of you age. You
behave differently in each stage. Well,
so do countries. And so there is a
pattern that happens that when a country
gets too much debt, when a country gets
where people expect too much without
working very hard, and you can look all
the way back to Roman times, you can
look at what's happened, you know, to
the British Empire. there is a period of
time in which someone else becomes the
challenger and right now China is that
challenger for us by far when that
occurs you have some conflict and the
conflict will often happen even more so
if there's conflict within the country
as well so we not only have debt we have
several of these elements we have
internal conflict in our country where
really we've used social media to a
great extent and other actors outside of
us have actually augmented this to
create more conflict internally that
makes you weaker right we're out
spending money all around the world on
different wars. China is keeping
everything central and playing go. We're
playing chess. If you don't understand
the difference, go is a million times
more complex, but go is much slower.
You're gradually, before somebody knows
it, taking over their territory. You're
not going straight into a war. It's kind
of like the art of art of war. So, we're
in a place right now where we have to
cut back on our expenses, but no one's
doing it. Neither party's doing it. And
so, he's raising the flag saying we
can't have more. We're going to have we
have a trillion dollars worth of debt
that we're interest we're paying this
year.
>> Well, I mean, I'll answer the question
is that nobody wants to address that
issue because it's certainly not popular
and politicians forever have not wanted
to do it because it doesn't get them
elected to do it. But we're right now in
August where they were projecting we
were going to be at the end of the year.
>> $40 trillion. So he said on the brink,
his words. Yes,
>> I believe we are currently on the brink.
Yes,
>> I'm worried about something worse than a
recession. if this isn't handled well,
worse than a recession, depression is
kind of what he's talking about now.
>> He's also worried about, you know, civil
strife. He's worried about all those
elements together. So, they're all
legitimate. I I bring him out to talk.
He's a dear friend. He sent me a note
the other day. He said, you know, he
said, uh, there's a Chinese proverb that
says, "A rabbit has many holes." He
said, "How many other holes do you have
in the world and make sure you're in
great shape?" So yes, I think it's a
very serious issue, but I think what the
only way to solve it is by individuals
actually pressing on their politicians.
But right now, we have politicians on
both sides that take advantage of
whatever's going on the environment for
more power. It has nothing to do with
what serves the American people, right?
And so it doesn't look good for us to
solve it. But here's what I know about
human history. Usually it takes a crisis
for us to wake up. You look at a
business, even in my own business
careers, I can say you you you look at
Blockbuster. Blockbuster. Well, they
weren't dumb people. How did they go out
of business, they could have bought
Netflix for $50 million. They ah, you
know, we need them. They were everything
was going so well for so long that all
of a sudden it didn't do well. They did
not recover. Other companies found a way
to recover. They saw what was happening.
The crisis happened and it made them
come up with a new way to do things. So,
I think crisis creates breakthroughs.
Some of those breakthroughs are painful.
Some of those breakthroughs are going to
be very, very they're going to make a
better life for all of us. We do have
some capacity to deal with that debt by
becoming more productive. And he talks
about that AI is one of that
possibilities, but we're not getting the
AI to produce the level of result yet
that gives us that massive jump in
productivity because you got to look at
your assets and your liabilities. If you
talk to people that look at this country
and say, "What are all our resources?"
That includes all of our resources below
the ground, everything that we have. The
ratio of debt compared to our real full
resources is something that's completely
manageable in the minds of those people.
But are we at coming to a place where
this is gonna people are going to have
to have a reckoning? I believe the
answer is absolutely yes.
>> I wonder who's going to take the lead on
this because you're right, you can't win
an election by hey, we're going to cut
the debt and during my term I'm going to
make sure we're going to cut some
entitlement programs, less spending on
military, less spending on this. I don't
want this guy to be elected. It's going
to be such easy fear porn coming against
this guy. So it's it's almost as if
Supreme Court I don't even know how you
put it through supreme someone needs to
say hey we're the board of America you
can't be doing that
>> it's going to be a crisis that does it
>> so I mean people takes a crisis for
people burning type of thing
>> like when people overuse a drug and
that's what we've been doing with
capital to a certain extent right the
overuse drug we've been spending that's
been our drug
>> we are bloated
>> what happens to a point there's a point
when you keep trying to get more in and
you get less of a high and then there's
a point where you finally hit a crisis
and you either die out of that crisis or
you transform I think we're going to
have a crisis. There's no question about
it.
>> The way the way I love what you guys
said, which is very important, is the 8
8 to 12 uncorrelated investments to make
sure even if it happens, you know,
there's going to be certain things that
are going to perform well during that
season. But if you're 100% just in one
area, like when you put you put hold on
S&P 500 or sell, which one did you put?
You put sell. So, if you're only an S&P
5 and you know back in the days they
used to say, "Well, just put your money
in investment company active America
with American funds or go to Troll Price
or all this other stuff." Yeah, those
days are behind us.
>> So, So, okay. So, maybe let me
>> You're not trying to time the market.
>> No, I'm not trying to time them. I can't
do that. That's Nobody does that. Nobody
does that, right? So, okay. So, give me
the hedge. Would your hedge against a
massive crisis that could be a 40% type
of a correction that
>> Ray Ray's hedge is in money master the
game and it basically is what we're
doing which is he calls it the all-w
weatherather portfolio and he's figured
out for example this is somewhat complex
so make it simple when people think
about stocks and bonds and they go I'm
50/50 I'm split the difference you're
not 50/50 because stocks are three times
more volatile than bonds okay so the
idea of a 6040 50/50 is based on an
illusion based on the level of risk.
It's not that. That's why people get a
result that they're really unhappy with.
So, he has laid out and I've laid out in
my book the exact balance of how to put
yourself in. So, if one thing goes up,
the other ones down, vice versa, so that
you end up with a balanced portfolio
that isn't the most aggressive thing
that'll, you know, give you the highest
returns, but it'll protect you in all
weather, any season, any environment
you're in. He's the master of that. And
what we did is we took that exact same
concept which for all of those that are
in the financial industry know that
Marowitz won the Nobel Prize for modern
portfolio theory. What Ray did such a
great service is he made that actually
understandable for a whole lot of
people. And what we did is we took the
all-weather concept and we applied it to
the true less correlated assets that are
the private markets. So when you have
private market assets that definitely
have less correlation and you combine
them with the overall philosophy of the
all-wheeler portfolio, that's how you
get to what we refer to as the holy
grail of investing. That is what
ultimately allows people to ride through
that. I do want to come back to one
thing you said. There is actually a
solution that doesn't require a crisis.
It's not very popular, but it is a
reality that the American people do have
the power to actually fix the debt
problem themselves without worrying
about politicians. and that is a
constitutional convention where they say
we're going to pass a balanced budget
amendment. Now, there's a lot of pain
that comes with that and there's a lot
of hurdles to do that, but that actually
is within the constitution. The rights
of the American people, if they stand
up, are unified, then they absolutely
can make a difference. But I don't know
if that's going to happen in my lifetime
or not. And we have to prepare the
investments in case it doesn't. And we
want to have that all-weather portfolio
using the best of the public markets and
the best of the private markets and
every investor can.
>> And by the way, if you're watching this
right now and you're you're part of the
camp that's like, "Oh my god, that's why
I'm so scared
>> and and that's why I'm just not going to
get into the market because what if it
does happen?" Well, if you don't and it
does happen and the next 5 10 years of
market goes, you missed out on so much.
You know, the whole thing of if you go
back and you know 20 years and you miss
the six best days.
>> That's right. the the difference between
the amount of money you would lose it's
in the if depending on how much money
you you lose so much money in return for
it to be fear-based
>> and by the way the best days are usually
within two weeks of the worst days if
you take a look at history and people
are panicked and they stay out of it
that's also why having assets and
something that aren't quite as liquid
where you've got people why has private
equity done so well when the stock
market they don't drop as much and they
return faster how is that because they
don't have to sell
>> when everybody's going crazy they just
like as if you and your own person real
estate. They own business. They
>> You don't even have a choice. You got to
stay locked in.
>> We got cash flow. We don't have to do
anything. We keep running the business.
Now, maybe we buy during that time, but
we sell when the market goes higher
again. And that's why they're able to
produce these magnitudes of wealth.
Look, if you look at the Fortune, you
know, 400 and say, who are the people
who are the wealthiest in the country?
What is the industry they're in? Most
people say tech completely wrong. Real
estate completely wrong. Medical wrong.
It's And by the way, it it is not hedge
funds because they come and go. It's
private equity because these guys are
not trying to time something. They're
buying an asset. Same thing you and I do
in business, right? You and I have done
this many times. Get a business and what
do we do? Add massive value. Transform
the team. Bring a new CEO. Bring in the
AI. Change the marketing. Grow that
business and sell it for a multiple to
another business or take it public.
That's what they do. It's a very
different formula. It's not like the old
days where they took something, divided
it up, and sold off all the pieces and
put it all in debt. Those days are over
for the most part today. And in fact,
one of the biggest differences today
since 2008 and Bane was the one that
started this is the alignment. Maybe you
should mention about the alignment.
>> So, you know, what changed for most
people in the investment world is trying
to get more aligned with their investors
and Bane was the first one to really do
this after 2008 to convince people to go
into their fund. They put a billion
dollars of their own money into the
fund. Okay, that's a lot of money. That
obviously gives people confidence that
they're aligned. We have a saying as a
firm that we're freakish about
alignment. So, everything is about
alignment. We have the we're the largest
investor in everything that we do. We've
got $750 million of our own money
invested in our own vehicles. So we
always lead with our own money. That's
alignment. Doesn't mean it's going to
work, but it means we're aligned.
>> But I mean you if we're not willing to
bet our money, why should you but your
own?
>> Exactly. But so what happened is is the
industry's continued to grow. The
ability to raise funds is highly
dependent on how much of your own
capital you're going to put in, which is
typically 2 to 5% of whatever it is. So
just use 5% because it makes the math
easy. You raise a billion dollar fund,
you got to put up 50 million of your own
money. That's great. You have good track
record. You want to raise a $2 billion
fund, now it's hundred million. You want
to raise a $5 billion fund, now it's
$250 million. And you hadn't gotten your
50 back. So, where you going to get the
money? That's why people will sell a
stake to firms like ours because of the
fact that they need growth capital to be
able to reinvest in their business, be
able to grow, and oh, by the way, when
they raise that $5 billion fund, they're
going to get 2% management fee on
average, some higher, some lower. And
they're going to get literally that
billion dollar. Okay. Over a course of
five years just from managing that
portfolio. Five years. I'll use 10
billion. 10 billion. Billion is five
years is 10 years.
>> Two. Yeah. So $200 million on a $10
billion fund. Do that for 5 years
because it's locked up. It's
contractually obligated. You're talking
about a billion dollars. Oh, by the way,
you take that 10 billion, you turn it
into 20 billion. You get paid 20% of the
profit. So you make an extra two
billion. That's what the opportunity is
to own a private asset management firm.
Whether it be a $500 million firm, a $5
billion firm, or a $10 billion firm,
that's why people will sell a stake. And
if we buy, let's say, 13% of somebody's
position, they still got 87%. We're very
aligned. And that economic outcome is
what makes owning a private asset
management firm such an attractive
business model. I mean, imagine this.
You've got a lot of different
businesses. Imagine if you had customers
who are not allowed to fire you and they
have to give you a five-year contract.
It's pretty easy to budget if you know
your revenue for the next five years.
And oh, by the way, if you have a
billion dollar fund, it takes you 20
people. If you raise a $2 billion fund,
it doesn't take you 40 people. It might
take you another five or six. So, you
have this huge operating leverage. The
average operating margin for private
asset management firms just from
management fees is 60%. Profit margins.
Then on top of that they get the carry.
Then on top of that they get the return
on their money they put in their own
fund and they get the growth of the
enterprise value because if they grow
from three billion to 30 billion
obviously they're worth a lot more
money. And we now have over a hundred
different firms that we own stakes in
that manage collectively$ 2.9 trillion
dollars in assets. and have 12 billion
of contractually obligated management
fees over the next 10 years. They don't
even ever have to raise another dollar
and they're going to make $12 billion of
revenue. That's the sustainability which
is not correlated.
>> How hard is it to get into the business?
>> Oh, it's very very hard. It's extremely
hard.
>> What does it take to create a PE firm
>> and succeed? You got to have a great
track record. You got to have people
that believe in you and then you got to
deliver performance.
>> What's the So, okay. So, if I'm if I
talk about putting a winning team, I'm
talking to Tom Pen. I asked him this
question because he used to do the
remember he used to do the collective
bargaining agreements on ESPN. He was so
good at it. I love when he does it. But
if I want to put a winning team and I
ask uh Shaq or the late Kobe or Magic I
said what matters the most. The owner
the coach the player superstar you know
GM what are the and then they would all
give their philosophy and what's the
most important hire on a P. If somebody
wants to start a PE firm what are the
sequence five steps and what matters the
most? private equity firm, I would
answer, very different than private
credit or private real estate. But I'll
answer your question with PE. Yes,
>> you've got to have somebody who is the
superstar investor who can convince
people that they are the right person to
back. They obviously need strong
partners that are going to be able to
bring skill sets that are complimentary
to theirs. You have to have somebody who
has the relationship.
>> One is somebody like you.
>> That certainly is one way to do that.
with other firms that have and and to be
clear, there are firms that have
different formulas, but I'm going to
give you what I see the most common to
where you have somebody who's a dominant
personality, a dominant investor, who's
got a great track record. It builds a
team around them that allows them to
have enormous credibility to where
people know that what they do, they have
an edge. And that's the key. That's the
formula that most people don't have. Oh,
I'm going to go buy stuff and it's going
to be great. No, it can't be financial
engineering. They've got to be able to
add value. They got to be able to add
alpha, as we call it, in the industry.
So, what is it that they do that's
totally different? As an example,
there's a firm literally right down the
road from here called Trivest. One of
our favorite firms are one of our
largest positions. Tvest is an amazing
firm, 30 years old. All they do is
invest in founder and family-owned
businesses. They're the first
institutional capital in
those companies better. They buy it at,
let's just say, seven times cash flow.
They put a little bit of leverage on it.
They grow the business dramatically.
They make it more profitable, better
profit margins, professionalize
everything they're doing, and then
they're able to sell it at 10 to 12
times.
>> It's not a complicated strategy, but
literally in their history,
>> they have what they call the path to 3X.
They have done that on every fund
they've ever done
>> in 45 years
>> in in 30 35 years or so. So, they are a
systematic alpha creator across
generations of leadership, too. They've
actually had generational change over
that period of time.
>> So, I'm tracking So, so far I you need a
you need a Christopher. What's the two?
I need the four.
>> You definitely need at least two or
three other really solid investment
people, okay,
>> that know how to break down
opportunities to be able to build those
businesses once you've acquired your
your your stake or acquired the firm as
a whole. They're primarily control as an
example using them and I could give you
50 other examples. But in that case, you
also need to have somebody who's good at
relationship management. Somebody's got
to have the relationships with either
the institutions, the family offices or
other large pools of capital that are
going to give you money to manage. You
have to have a great operations
compliance regulatory person because
this is a very regulated
>> are you a series 766 what?
>> So we we are not a broker dealer. So all
we are is RA we're registered investment
advisor. That's all of our people are.
>> So let me let me the reason why I'm
asking this question. Say you have you
run a consult. This is a selfish
question here. This is purely for me. So
if you don't want to listen you want to
listen. It's up to you. So, say you have
a consulting firm that you get deals
that always come through to you.
>> Companies ranging from 5 million all the
way up to $385 million in IBIDA and we
consult for them. Could be multi-million
dollar engagement, but we have constant
deal flow coming in.
>> What do you do with the access to these
deals that are coming to you of
founders? They own majority of the
company and they would like to team up
with our firm. What do you do with the
access to these types of deals that are
coming your way?
>> It depends. It really is if you want to
be the investor in that opportunity that
you're helping to improve. I mean, the
vast majority of firms actually that's
what they really are to the firms that
they make act uh they acquire, right?
They're a consultant. They come in as an
adviser to be in the boardroom to say,
"Look, we got to make some tough
decisions. We got to set really good
goals. We got to make sure that we get
there." So, you can absolutely translate
that into a role of the investor in that
company. There's a lot of consulting
firms that take instead of a hard dollar
fee, they will actually take a percent.
do that as well, right? That's a way to
monetize that.
>> We'll do cash and equity.
>> That's right. Somebody could certainly
do a fund once they have a proven track
record. The key is for anybody, you got
to be able to show the good, the bad,
and the ugly and how you've done. You
can't cherrypick just the winners and
say, "Look how great I am." So, when you
have to, you know, we look at 2,000
investments a year. We might make 20 or
30 a year. So, somebody's got to
literally convince me and I'm not easy
to convince that they can actually do
this over and over and over and over
again in good markets, bad markets, and
that they're not just, you know,
somebody that's really
>> So, that follows it with another
question for you. So, when you look at a
deal coming in, uh, we scored a
eight-point system that we look at to
see if this is something for us to
entertain or not.
>> Uh, and we've made, god knows a lot of
mistakes. I mean, we made these mistakes
where it's like you, oh my god, I like
the guy's personally. Like, this is this
is not the way to do it,
>> right? What used to matter to you 20
years ago when you were a little bit
more green? Not ne you've been around
for 30 years, but what used to matter to
you 20 years ago where no longer
impresses you and what matters today
when you say I think this is something
we should invest in.
>> The track record itself impresses me
very little. It really does. And that's
something that will surprise a lot of
people. The track record obviously I
want to know it's there but more
importantly I want to know the why
behind it. Right? You know as an example
there was a great firm I mean well-known
firm I'm not going to use their name.
They came into the office a couple of
months ago. They have a fantastic track
record, but if you actually dig into it
in every single fund, they've had one
investment that has made basically the
entire track record real and everything
else was very mediocre and they've just
been able to do that every single fund.
Well, I don't want to be in the one
where they don't have that happen
>> and that everything is mediocre or that
everything is just average. But also
what matters to me and I think to most
great allocators is persistency not not
performance the persistency of the
performance
>> how do you measure that
>> so do they have every fund I mean
perfect example would be is every fund
is between 14 and a 16% internal rate of
return that's a lot of persistency
that's highly unusual but there's a
reason why they created that consistency
off of 5 6 7 8 10 funds if you have one
fund that's two and one fund that's 30
and one funds at three and one funds at
40 okay that's not persistent That's
inconsistency. I don't know which one
I'm going to get, the bad one or the
good one. So, what matters to me the
most is persistency. And the other thing
that really I didn't care about much
then, but I cared more is pedigree.
Okay. Yes. I want to know that they went
to a good school, they have a good
education,
>> but generally speaking, I don't care
that much.
>> Did that matter to you more?
>> Too much when I was 20 years old. Now,
it doesn't. I mean, I
>> Tell me why. Why? because of the fact
that there's some of the best schools
that put out some of the worst
investors, [laughter]
okay? And some some great investors,
too. But you cannot just say because
they went to X, Y, or Z that they're a
great investor. Certainly, I respect
their intellect to be able to go through
a great school. But that doesn't mean
they're a great investor. Some of the
smartest people I know in this industry
that could not make an investment to
save their life.
>> What's an eliminator? What is it like
the if I see these and your team knows,
guys, if I see these three things, don't
even bring the opportunity to me. What
are those things? First thing is if they
don't have an auditor, run. Don't don't
walk.
>> Auditor meaning like audited financials
like QV like quality of earnings type of
thing.
>> Not necessarily be a QE, but they better
have an audited financials. Okay.
There's no audit financials. I'm out.
Period. That's how we avoided maid off.
That entire story I could tell you.
That's how we avoided maid off.
>> Let me ask you, let's say a person
doesn't have it. Will you say, "Go do
your audited financials. Come back to
us."
>> Absolutely.
>> Okay. Kind of like if I'm a realtor and
I'm showing a million auto property, but
you don't even have pre-approval lender,
you know, bank that's giving it to you.
Kind of like that. Absolutely. And it's
got to be an auditor we know and it's
got to be one that we trust.
>> Top 50 like BKD like
>> I mean there's some specialties in
certain industries and sectors,
technology in particular. They don't
have to be that big, but we have to know
they've been around and that they're not
obviously conflicted.
>> What are the other two? The other two
would be basically where they have been
lucky, right? There's so many people
that have made a great track record
because they started at the right time.
There's some people we looked at the
other day, they started in 2009 in real
estate. You you had to pretty be stupid
to not make money in 2009 buying real
estate. Okay, there was 2006.
>> Different story.
>> That's a different story. So, and that's
the third thing.
>> You got destroyed.
>> I don't want them learning on my nickel.
Okay. I don't want somebody figuring it
out with my money. All right. They need
to have proven themselves through
different cycles.
>> I'm tracking. What's your third?
>> So, that's the third is they can't learn
on my nickel. So, the second is it can't
be that they just got lucky with their
record.
>> Got it. Okay. I mean, there's so many
times that I see people that they
literally got involved in something, you
know, in in healthcare or in technology
or in consumer and they just happen to
hit a lucky trend, right? But that
doesn't mean they could do it again.
>> Great feedback.
>> You see the the distinction of of being
willing to focus on what's the worst
case scenario and can you survive that?
Can you succeed from that? The level of
discipline that he has, the reason he's
got a 96% profitability rating over 25
years is the level of discipline. It's
90% of what we see, we'll never even can
consider. we'll look at and go deep but
not even consider because he has that
level of focus and discipline and that
level of discipline disappears when you
get excited about something based on the
track record based on the pedigree based
on whatever elements push your buttons
oh it's another AI company people then
stop evaluating with depth and this is
Christopher's greatest strength
>> I love it so different question complete
different direction we're going Tony
you're 2530 years old uh today you're
not Tony Robbins so because you're one
of one we can't we just you're a regular
2530 30-year-old today. You got a
regular job that you're doing. You're a
worker. You're doing your part. You want
to get married. You want to have kids.
You want to buy a house. What decisions
would you make before choosing a wife?
This is a very different question. 25,
26, 28 years old. I want to get married.
Tony, what advice would you give me
before choosing my wife?
>> About who you choose as your wife?
>> Who I choose as my wife?
>> Well, I think the most important thing
there is not just chemistry because
chemistry can go away for the time
being. And chemistry can be reignited
also. You can be with somebody for years
and have that be reignited because
chemistry is really based upon opposite
energies, masculine and feminine
energies. If both people are feminine
and their energies, I'm not being
meaning gay or both men or both women,
>> just opposite energies, right? If that
opposite energy there, there's polarity
and polarity creates excitement and
energy just like opposite poles of North
and South Pole or you go to plug
something electricity, there's two
plugs. We have to have that. If we both
become the same, a relationship loses
polarity. And when it loses polarity,
you start to become judgmental in the
relationship. Things that you thought
were cute, now you begin to go, why do
they always do that? Why does he always
tell that story? Why does she always Why
does she take that long? And you get
annoyed by things because the attraction
is not there. So chemistry is not the
place. Here's what you need to
understand relationship. What makes a
relationship work is things in common.
What makes it passionate is differences.
Things in common is common values, maybe
some common dreams. If you come
together, I'll give you an example. I
was with a I bumped into a friend in
Fiji one time. This is years ago. We're
still flying commercially. We got there
and I have my resort there. And my wife
and I were just got married ourselves.
They only been together a short time.
And um we were crazy, both of us. And so
there's a line to go through
immigration. And I go, "Let's go line."
She goes, "No, let's go that line." I
said, "This is a better line." "No,
that's better." Fine. You go in your
line and go in my line. And so we do
this stupid little race. We were playful
back and forth. All of a sudden, a guy
behind me goes, "Tony." And I turn
around. Very famous guy. If I mention
his name, you know who it is. And he
goes, "I haven't seen you in years. How
you doing?" So, we started talking. I
said, "What are you doing here?" He
goes, "Well, I just got married. I'm
going to my honeymoon." I said, "It's
the third marriage." I said, "Wow." I
said, 'Well, where's your spouse or
where's your wife? You know, he goes,
"She's over there." And they're doing
the same thing. She's in the line over
there and she's right next to my wife,
right? So, we're laughing about it for a
minute. So, I asked him, you know, yeah,
how's it going? I haven't seen you in
all this time, maybe seven, eight years.
And and he, you know, he's very
successful, really brilliant guy. And I
asked him, you know, how they met? and
he was involved with professional
volleyball, just put it that way. And so
she got involved. And so I, you know,
I'm talking. I said, "So, uh, how long
you known each other?" And he says,
"Gosh, I think Tony, I met her right
around the time I met you. Probably
eight years." I said, "Wow, you're just
getting married now. How come?" He goes,
"She wormed me down." And I thought,
"Oo, so like, so I thought, well, what
do you say?" So I said, "Well, so you're
going to have kids, right?" He goes,
"Hell no." He goes, "You know, I've been
through two other marriages. I've
already got kids. I'm not doing this."
And I look across and she's 28 years old
and he's, you know, mid-40s, let's say,
maybe a little more than that. And I
said to him, "Have you guys talked about
this?" And he said, "Oh yeah." He goes,
"That was the deal. If we get married,
no kids." So I'm thinking in my head, he
doesn't understand. They're not aligned.
And he just he's convincing himself
they're aligned, right, on something
really important like kids. That doesn't
mean you have to be identical in your
goals and dreams, but on this, you got
to have some alignment in nature. So
sure enough, we're going to immigration.
We introduce each other to each other's
spouses. And I look at my wife and she
looks at me after they left. I said,
'What'd you learn?' She goes, 'What did
you learn?' I said, ' They're screwed.
[laughter]
And I told him, I I said, he said, 'N
not going to have kids. She goes, I told
talk to her. She said, he says we're not
have them, we'll have them within two
years. And they did and they are
divorced, his third divorce. And he lost
half of everything he had again because
he just didn't understand alignment.
Just like alignment in a business,
right? People say like, how can you
trust somebody? Well, you can't just
trust them based on their past behavior.
You trust them by having interest
aligned. You could trust an enemy. If I
lose and you lose, I win, you win. You
got to trust the enemy. I don't believe
in enemies, but you know what I mean?
Yeah. So, you have to have alignment.
And so, in a relationship, what makes it
work is do you have values and
alignment? Do you have some things that
are doesn't have to be identical?
>> What makes it alive though is
differences, masculine feminine
energies, different energies. And
sometimes it starts that way. And then
you go through the stress of life and
both people get really pleasing, real
feminine energy, or both people get
really tough. And when they're both the
same, there's no opposite energy. And
you lose that and then the relationship
starts to break down because people go
through a cycle of then judging each
other, then feeling like they're not
enough or feeling I'm not loved enough
or respected enough and then they get
their interest somewhere else in work or
with their kids and they drift away. So
the number one question you need to ask
yourself about being in a relationship
is 80% of success in a relationship is
selection. They'll say, "Thank you very
much. Why don't you tell me before I
married this idiot?" No, no. I you don't
understand who you select to be in that
relationship. See, in the beginning of
relationship,
>> who you select to be a
>> part of you select to show up.
>> Yeah. Who you select to be married to.
>> That's right. Cuz in the beginning of
relationship, everybody selects their
best person. Yeah. You over I'm going do
everything for you. I love whatever it
takes. Take out the trash. I'll take out
the trash. Whatever it takes. Right now,
after seven days, seven weeks, seven
months, seven years, 70 years, LIKE TAKE
OUT THE TRASH. TAKE IT OUT YOURSELF.
WANT TO LOOK LIKE A JANITOR? RIGHT? So
if you I always tell people if you do
what you did in the beginning of the
relationship there won't be an end to
the relationship right but you got to
select people often times they change
the rules once they get married or once
they start living with someone different
than they were pursuing and that will
cost you no matter what you do. But it's
often times making sure you're aligned
on values, finding an alignment on the
most important goals. They have to all
be the same so you're not in conflict at
a deep level. And then it's who are you
showing up as? Because your state is
what you bring to that relationship.
>> Okay. So now let's let's go a little bit
deeper. I'm I'm your son. I'm 18 years
old. I'm 22 years old. I'm 25 years old.
What are you telling me to look out for?
You know how Charlie Munger would always
at dinner his kids say he would always
talk about the mistakes his friends
made. Yes.
>> What are you warning me against in life?
>> Making a choice too soon before you know
what's really what what who this could
be general. This could be general to
start with. But also getting getting my
kids and all of them. I've had these
conversations with them. Getting them to
really see that they have their own
sense of identity and they're not
running to something else to heal them
or to solve them. It's like you got to
solve what's in yourself. So you bring
something to a relationship. If you're
going to relationship to get something,
it's already upside down. If you're
going to relationship to give something,
you feel alive. What makes you feel
alive is being loving. People say, "I
want love." Well, be loving, you know.
But today, so much of our society has
been focused on ourselves. So much of
the anxiety we have in our society, so
many young people, is because we've been
so protected that everything's about
getting what we want. Not getting what
you want is one of the most important
things in life. Remember the old days
when they were talking about the secret?
I remember you know think positive
>> bewit was in it but I remember all the
guys that were
>> they invited me to participate say I
will not participate in this I said it's
not that there isn't an attraction
principle of course there is thoughts
are attractive but that's not the only
principle that affects human beings are
you telling me like the guy that cut my
hair is a kind of a rocker guy and he
said to me the day I was here in LA and
he comes to me and he goes or I was in
LA at the time and he goes I I've been
doing that secret thing and I'm I got
all green lights I said what are you
going to do when you get all red lights
you going to say something wrong with me
I said you going to tell me the people
that went to Ashwitz were negative
thinkers sometimes not getting what you
want is the universe's way so that you
grow and become someone who can now
bring something to the world. So it
isn't all about get what I want. And by
the way, when you get all you want
easily, you're never happy. Right? You
and I both know the stuff people who sit
around the table at this stage of my
life who are my friends who've achieved
incredible things in their life. We
usually talk about the early tough times
the most part, right? Like I had a a
dinner with a bunch of people all they
called it the goats dinner. Everybody
there is considered the greatest of all
time. What they do some athletes, some
people in fashion, some people in
entertainment, people in sports, myself,
movies. And the whole conversation was
mostly about all the things that we went
through and the joy of where we are
today cuz you can't have a foreground
without a background.
>> Mhm.
>> Right. It's that contrast that makes
life feel alive. So if you just get
everything, you take everything for
granted. When you start giving things,
that's when you become more. Then you
like it's like you can take away
everything I have, all the toys or
trinkets or economics or whatever you
want to call it, acknowledgement from
other people. You can't take away who
I've become as a man in the process. who
you become, that's what makes you really
happy or really sad. What you get is not
going to do that.
>> 20s advice for career. Tony, what do I
do my career? What do I do? Where do I
go? Do I go into real estate? Do I
become a influencer? Do I go create a
podcast? Do I go into PE? What do I do?
What do you tell them?
>> It depends on what your passions are,
right? You want to find passions and
skill together. Passions and competence
together. You might have a passion for
singing. I have a passion for singing,
but listen to this voice. It's not going
anywhere, right? [laughter] I can speak,
but I'm not going to be disappointed.
Great voice, though. So it's like you
need to have a passion, but you also see
what am I aligned with? And the way you
do that to find your passion. First of
all, stop trying to think there's one
purpose in your life. This whole thing
of I don't know my young people. I don't
know my purpose. I got to find my
purpose.
>> Who said you had one purpose?
>> I have a different purpose when I'm
hanging out with my brother, than when I
am with my daughter, than I'm sitting
down with you versus if we're going to a
business meeting together. There's
different purposes in life. Stop
thinking there's one purpose. Secondly,
>> take a look and let something hit you.
Get around where it's better. Get around
people that are happier. Get around
people that love what they do. If you
think you're interested in private
equity or you think you're interested in
play musician, go shadow somebody. Go
see what their life is really like. What
you think it's like and live with that
for a few days and then you start to
understand. Then also find out what it
really takes. You look at somebody like
Steph Curry and go, "Wow, it's amazing.
He makes that shot. He's so he does it
from half court. He doesn't even look
turns." But, you know, he makes 500
shots a day in practice. 3,500 shots,
168,000 shots a year, 15 years, 2.5
million shots in practice to make to
make 3,600 shots in his career and be
the best in the world. 99% of what he
did was behind the scenes. That's
what'll make you successful. So, you do
got to see what it takes because
otherwise you have a delusion if I just
do that, I'm going to be happy. It's not
how it works.
>> Can we finish up with another game? Is
that okay with you?
>> Sure, go for it. Let's do another game.
All right.
>> So, buy, sell, hold, watches. Okay. I
don't know if you're into watches. I
know he is. You are. So you are. I can
see you are as well. All right. So here
we go. [laughter] PC.
>> Uh I I'm I'm a hold on that one myself.
>> Okay. You're hold.
>> That's all I buy.
>> Okay. Good. I respect it. All right.
Rolex.
>> Um it's a buy. It depends on the one
that you're going to do for the
>> I'd hold it if I had it, but I'm I I
just do.
>> You don't have any Rolex.
>> I just do PC.
>> Forgive us. Forgive us that we're not
totally right. I get that. I I I like PC
as well. Okay. RM
>> that's pretty much all aware of the
exceptionist today.
>> Don't know it and know of it, but
certainly wouldn't wouldn't buy it, but
I would hold it.
>> You ever seen this giant on stage with
his RM that he walks around everybody?
>> I have I I was given one by uh Shake
Tune. I said I I'm not going to spend
half a million dollars on a watch is
absurd. And he gave me one and it was so
light and you know me clapping and
moving all this stuff and all these
other watches I destroy. I will go this
day because I'm not going to be clapping
a movie. [laughter] Otherwise, this
watch is Yeah. is going to go out the
door. It's going to be destroyed. I love
those watches. I think they're
phenomenal.
>> How many do you have? How many RMS do
you have now?
>> Uh, eight.
>> Oh, okay. So, that gift led to you
buying a few.
>> I bought actually my wife has bought
them for me. They're they're more like
an investment and they've gone up in
value. Those watches don't
>> and you buy directly from them. So,
you're probably getting it, you know,
50%. I know how that So, AP, where you
at with AP?
>> I'm wearing one.
>> So, you like AP?
>> Uh, I like AP. They don't hold up with
my demands. If I'm wearing a dress
watch, it's a nice watch.
>> Okay. Best way to build influence.
You've done this podcast today. Books,
live events today.
>> Uh podcast is the largest reach today
because people are doing that by far. Um
but the only way you build a brand is by
adding value. So you do that here in a
podcast. If you did an event, you better
add massive value. Whatever you're going
to do, it's not the vehicle, it's the
value. If you overd deliver for people
consistently, you build a brand and
people will seek you out. Folks, we got
smarter today. I got smarter. I hope you
did as well. This was phenomen
I'm going to put the link below. They
were given 100% of the money of this to
feeding America to feed people.
>> Beautiful. So, do we drive it to this
website or do you want it to go to
Amazon? What would you like them to do
or doesn't matter?
>> Doesn't matter. They go where they want.
>> So, go order the book, The Holy Grail of
Investing. And uh as well as a couple of
the other things that we talked about
the the link to your to what you guys
do. Where do they go for the the
investment? cazinvestments.com
cazinvestments.com.
>> Can you go to cassinvestments.com? If I
go there, I want to learn about the
$2,500 investment. What do I do here to
to participate?
>> So, individual investors would select on
the left and investment professionals
obviously on the right, but left
somebody would be able to do that.
>> Can you do me a favor? Go back and click
on individual investors on the right.
>> Click on the right. There you go.
Individual investors. And then
>> so we've got videos that help educate
people about everything that we do. And
then obviously if they want to learn
specifically about any of our funds,
they click on the our funds and that
will take them to a full list. They log
in, they'll then get credentials to be
able to access that. We're you know an
SEC registered investment adviser. We
have to have protection for the investor
for all the SEC rules we have to comply
with. But from there they can get access
instantaneously to learn about all of
the funds we have.
>> There you go. So order the book and go
visit the uh fund and learn more about
it. Tony,
>> keep as usual. Christopher, pleasure.
Great having you on. Take care
everybody. God bless. Bye-bye. Bye-bye.
>> Handmade in Portugal, where
craftsmanship is a way of life. For
those who move through life differently,
from sunlit decks to knights that never
need an occasion. Every detail is
considered. [music]
Every step effortless,
crafted from fine suede and built with
builder [music] technology, designed to
move with you. Because true luxury isn't
about being noticed. It's about how you
feel when you arrive. The FLB Icon
loafer [music]
made for the life you've earned.